Remember in using a backhoe sometimes jobs may be from place to place.
So you might have a need to drive a backhoe from one job to another.
Including on the state highway.
Okay remember before you drive a backhoe on the public highway make sure all your safety items are in tact.
Including lights, flashers, make sure all your safety pins like boon lock, the rear swing lock, make sure all those items are in tact.
Make sure your bucket is down low where you have good visibility.
Four wheel drive is disengaged.
You do not need four wheel drive on a highway.
So when you're traveling down a highway make sure all the safety factors you can think of is in place.
Remember in highway travel always make sure your brake lock is in place.
So when you mash your foot both brakes will apply.
If you make the mistake and mash one brake on the highway it may cause you to drift over into other lanes or toward the ditch.
So make sure both brakes are locked so you'll have equal braking on both sides.